## Summary

I'm a 19 year old junior Information Systems Major from Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, currently attending Coastal Carolina University. I have over 7 years of experience programming, and almost just as much with graphic design and web development.

# Experience

#### Photographer at Ripley's Aquarium March 2013 - September 2013

Digital Communication Program at The Academy for the Arts, Science, and Technology

August 2012 - June 2014

Internship at Native Sons: Screenprint and Embroidery

January 2013 - March 2013

## Education

#### Carolina Forest High School

August 2010 - June 2012

The Academy for The Arts, Science, and Technology

August 2012 - June 2014

### Horry Georgetown Technical College

August 2014 - June 2015

## Coastal Carolina University

August 2016 - June 2018 (expected)

### Contact

- http://andrewault.me
- □ contact@andrewault.me
- /andyault
- ∂ /andyault
- **⋓** @krazy\_nd
- ☑ @krazy\_nd
- ★ 3432 Picket Fence Lane Myrtle Beach, SC 29579
- **(843)** 504-7218

## Skills

#### Proficient in:

HTML

JavaScript

AngularJS

Node.JS

Express

CSS

Less

Sass

PHP

Laravel

MongoDB

SQL

Lua

Java

C#

Unity

#### Experienced with:

Python 2.7

**VB.NET** 

 $\mathbb{C}^{++}$ 

ActionScript 2

#### Proficient with:

Adobe Master Collection

Illustrator

Photoshop

InDesign

DreamWeaver

After Effects

Git/Version Control

#### Microsoft Office

Word

Powerpoint

Excell